[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Champagne is usually served in a champagne flute at what temperature?", "correct_answer": "7 to 9 \u00b0C", "incorrect_answers": ["13 to 15 \u00b0C", "10 to 12 \u00b0C", "1 to 5 \u00b0C"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the three astronauts from Apollo 11 remained in the command module while the other two separated along with the lunar module?", "correct_answer": "Michael Collins", "incorrect_answers": ["Neil Alden Armstrong", "Edwin Eugene Buzz Aldrin, Jr.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the discipline of biology dedicated to the study of fungi called?", "correct_answer": "Mycology", "incorrect_answers": ["Fungitics", "Myology", "Fungology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor received the Razzie Award for Worst Actor for 1987?", "correct_answer": "Bill Cosby for Leonard Part 6", "incorrect_answers": ["Sylvester Stallone for Over the Top", "Ryan ONeal for Tough Guys Dont Dance", "Judd Nelson for From the Hip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The horror movie Dr. Jekyll  Sister Hyde was released in 1971.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first sub-Saharan African nation to gain its freedom?", "correct_answer": "Ghana", "incorrect_answers": ["Somalia", "Malawi", "Gabon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these Bernardo Bertolucci films does Liv Tyler play a leading role?", "correct_answer": "Stealing Beauty", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sheltering Sky", "The Dreamers", "La Luna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Kirby put his fake leg after fighting Scooter in the movie Dead Presidents?", "correct_answer": "on the dashboard", "incorrect_answers": ["in the backseat", "in the trunk", "back on his body"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At its peak, how many members did the Shinsengumi group have?", "correct_answer": "300+", "incorrect_answers": ["50+", "200+", "100+"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lightning is caused by the increased imbalance of positive and negative charges during storms.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor voiced the guinea pig character called Rodney in the 1998 comedy movie Dr. Dolittle?", "correct_answer": "Chris Rock", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Carrey", "Chris Tucker", "Eddie Murphy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "They were a group of landed nobility in Prussia  and Eastern Germany. Their name comes from the German for young lord. They formed several aristocratic political groups in Germany.", "correct_answer": "Junkers", "incorrect_answers": ["Jurrsia", "Jongres", "Junists"]}]